Bottom!
Two, one, pusher!
There you go!
One more!
Aaahhh!
I missed!
Who's there?
Come here.
Good morning, sir.
What's this?
That one looks good, too.
It is, isn't it? Yes.
Okay, we should be able to get a shot.
Oh, my God, your hair looks so good today.
Hello.
I'm off.
Wait.
Good morning.
Funny.
It's an in-person meeting today.
I want to go home.
It's a cat.
What is it today?
I think it's a cat.
A cat.
It's almost Halloween.
Yay!
Cat bread.
Ta-da!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm Momo kun!
I'm going to have a face-to-face meeting today.
Halloween and cats
Today is the second day.
Yesterday I was Bunny
but today I'm playing as Spider-chan.
I cut my hair.
I'll just have this one.
What's today's fashion point, Melon?
Why are you wearing the same Martin?
No, no, no!
I don't know.
You'll never see it.
Today it's a peace!
Yes, it is.
Today's fashion
Unexpectedly
To be able to wake up the hand
I'm here in hydrogen.
It looks great!
I'm also wearing the main outfit from Momo Kyun.
It looks good on you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I want you to.
Hello.
What's today's fashion point?
Core Bock.
What's your favorite part?
The ribbon.
It's so cute!
It's kind of, like, sporty in a sporty way, right?
Yes, it is!
Also, there's an M for Milten and a P for Pium.
Pium Milten. That's what it means.
And, you can put everything else in these pockets.
It's great!
This is, you know, the tunnel-style pen.
That's right. You can even hold your hands.
You can hold hands, too.
That's great.
Oh, there's so many!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow!
This way!
Hello!
Yay!
What's this?
Here you go.
Oh, this is the Eco-majority channel.
Subscribe to our channel!
Heart.
Is that a freestyler?
Oh, it's Othello, indeed.
Othello.
Wah!
Wow!
First of all, Kiara-senpai has a habit of...
She has a habit of mirroring... filing. For example, when I say, "Yes," she says, "Right? I say, "I'm a mirror.
So I was told that today, too. I was told by a star that I look so cute today. Her hair, her clothes...
My hair, my clothes, my hair, my clothes. I got dressed up and they said I was just dressed up.
It's really bad!
I'm really a mirroring demon.
Yeah!
Ah!
Come here.
What?
Wow.
Just now. Just now.
Just now.
What's that look on your face?
You're so cute.
No, no, no. This way.
Come here.
Rooty.
Aww...
I'm gonna fall over if you mew on me.
I'm sorry. It hurts like hell.
He's so cute.
Cute.
Chocolate. Chocolate.
Chocolate, you did that hat.
You said it was hard to hear you. How was it? Today.
But, you know, just a little bit of a gap in the ear,
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You went through with it.
You went through the crew.
Here today,
There were lots of animals here today, a cat, a bear here, a rabbit here, a dog with flowers hanging down here, and I thought it was this one, but it was Hana-sui.
Too cute, but too human I thought.
Yes, it is.
It's kind of cute, but...
If I laugh, I'll tell you a story and you'll be able to answer.
What? Cute!
You know, I don't want you to say that.
All I can say is "cute.
I'll only be able to say "cute.
No, that goes for seniors too.
In the love section...
It's Ogi-chan!
It's Ogi-chan! So cute!
Angel wings?
Oh, no, angel wings.
Mob-mob.
Cute. Cute triangles.
Excuse me.
I'll be alone.
Oh, really?
Ayame.
Uh, sure.
I don't know how to put this Tila Piquet thing on.
It's pretty, isn't it? In a kimono.
Tilasha's smell together.
Cute.
Because the belt, you know, they're almost the same.
They're the same.
Maybe one of us is facing the wrong way.
Listen, one of us is facing the wrong way with the belt.
What? Is there such a thing as the wrong side of the belt?
Of course there is.
If you're right-handed, do it.
Pause.
That's right, that's right.
Left-handed.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
Cherries!
I've got it! Cherry!
I did it!
I lifted my bangs and they fell out beautifully.
Really?
Isn't it really good?
It's so cute!
When I came home, I said, "Oh, it's so cute!
Oh! New character! New character!
Aya! New face!
Come here. Come here.
New face.
Please watch the channel, while you film!
Oh, that's great!
Oh, Mr. Tomi!
Oh, Tomi!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle!
Cute kids!
They all seem to have the same sentiments.
Wait, am I not tiny?
Usually there are only kids smaller than me.
I'm so tiny when I'm surrounded by girls like you.
How unusual!
Oh, my God!
Balance.
There are so many!
So many
I'm so happy
Please tell me it's been more than a year since I've seen a heart!
I just went and did it... it doesn't matter who it is...
I don't want to hang up on you.
I don't want to hang up on you, so I'll tell you what I meant.
I don't want to cut it off...
They were the smallest.
I'm the biggest.
See?
Equal love.
I'll be right there.
What, is this a TV?
What?
Oh, it's on?
Oh, my God.
It's on?
Oh, my God, it's on! It's on!
It's great. It's great.
We're a group called Equal Love.
Nice to meet you.
I play an instrument.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's autumn, isn't it?
Aren't they cute?
Isn't it amazing how you guys look in these?
It's coming out of here.
You know, I can hear people who can hear me.
Well, you can't hear them if you're wearing a hat or something... if you're a fan.
But this one's open like that.
It's amazing.
I can hear the fans.
I'm off.
You want me to show you something?
Can I say hello to them?
You're the leader, please.
Make it up, guys.
It's already too hot today.
What are you doing?
I'm Aimi Ozawa from Nearly Called Due
Yuka Murayama
This is my Ichiki.
No, no, no...
Yes, yes, yes.
This is my Chainz.
Yay!
They're all girly, aren't they?
Girly.
I'm Akira.
Make sure you get a good picture of me.
Hello.
That's all I want.
That's all I have.
What can I do?
I'll just say "choo-choo.
Hey, little girl.
Comment!
Please do.
I'd love to hear from you.
Comment separate
ised
Let's be in the same class for the additional show!
I'll be there!
I'm also active here in Clarimesse.
Cute!
There are a lot of animals here!
Animals will be animals
Here come the animals!
Here we go.
Here are today's Animals.
It's full of critters.
Here are the creatures... all of them.
They're so cute!
This is Crahan, and this is his sister.
This is the Animals of the Day.
They imitate pandas.
Pandas eat.
It's really hot, isn't it?
They're so hot!
Natsui-kun...
This is fine.
I'll show you my today's coordinate.
Here we go.
Are you in the picture?
It's cute.
It's a high school girl style coord.
Like a coord.
I'm going to blow my favorite color in black.
Cute.
I was pinning it yesterday, too.
Today is the last day of my 24th year.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I got a lot of congratulations because it's today.
Thank you.
I'm having a very happy last day.
Thank you very much.
I'm Ichikkodan neru now.
Please give me a gold hawk.
Kintaka.
Then let's have him say something.
Momo kun
At that SC.
I'm ignoring you.
Iori-san seems to be on zero.
Oh, just me?
They all have their names on the board.
I have 20 circles, and Yuri's is black and white.
What's today's fashion party?
Today's fashion party is casual.
Nice!
Cute shoes.
They're cute.
They're all cute. Silver ones.
But you can probably get them all at ZooZoo.
Well then, look at them.
If you want to do that.
Cute.
Cute!
It's all Torreraka!
There's nothing but Torrelakas
So cute!
I got this!
I saw it.
You're looking at it, aren't you?
Thank you very much.
This way, this way.
This is Nanaka Tomita.
She's so cute.
I want to show you! I can't see!
Magazine model.
She's really cute today.
She's so stylish.
Expert
Did you do that yourself?
I did it myself.
What? That's amazing.
Look how big my arm is. Look how I bent it.
Oh, yeah.
Look at how I styled it. It's like it's about to float.
It's super cute.
And the hair, it's so good, it's all good.
It's all so good. I got the bangs short.
It's so good!
It's too stylish. Something.
Hey!
What's going on today?
It's a different story today, isn't it?
It's a different book.
What's that, too?
It's like a contrast.
It's pretty good, right?
Hi, come here.
No, no, no.
You don't mind if I don't?
You don't want to?
I have a bench blanket.
Oh, wow, that's great.
Why not?
I like it.
Because you're the only one who can do it.
That's right. You're the only one who can.
Cutie.
Pretty.
I kind of adore it.
Really?
I've seen it.
I've seen you do that a lot.
You're fighting me, aren't you?
I don't have much either.
I'm going to eat lunch.
I'm having lunch.
Well, let's let them talk here.
I'll see you in a minute.
I'm coming with you.
You left me.
Thanks for coming.
Come here.
I'm already in too many pictures.
I want to be in it with you.
You're in too many pictures.
I'm in too many pictures.
It's my first time.
For the third time.
One more time.
I love it.
Really?
I'm going out to eat tomorrow.
Actually, we're going out to eat tomorrow.
You're so dressed up today.
I love you so much today.
We just talked about it.
I'm sorry.
Do you think they'll use this?
I hope so.
Then let's do something that will be used.
I don't know.
You're persistent.
They'll use this.
Wait, what's this?
He's gonna be jealous of the killer. No, I'm not jealous of the killer.
Nanaka hugged me back, and I want Nanaka to do it, too.
So now she's jealous of me? They'll be jealous of everything I do. They'll just be mad at me.
Thank you. I think I'll call it a day.
Oh, that's right, because if we go past that, it'll be the fourth time.
I'll hold off then.
Okay, I'm going to go eat.
I'm going to the cafe.
Go, go!
Shoko.
So cute!
She's got her finger on it.
I didn't know you and Shoko got along so well.
You're good friends.
We've been home together.
That's right.
We're from Momonohoshi.
I see.
Of your own accord.
As you wish.
We're from the Peach Star, too.
I'm so happy.
That's so sweet.
Kind
Tinder.
Did you put your ears on just now?
I did. Partially.
I was wearing cat ears.
You were supposed to see the cat ears.
I catpunched him.
I hope they use them.
Here we go. Ready, go!
Meow.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye bye!
Fatty Rin
How's it going?
I want to talk.
We're done.
Hey, two days.
Hey.
Oh, my God...
Already, I mean...
It was just now, right?
Part one through three.
Oh, I see.
Because it was in the morning.
So, everyone come early next year.
Thank you.
Thanks for your help.
What's so far away?
Cute.
It's cute.
It's the end of the year.
How was it?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm not like you guys.
I look like a lot of people today.
When did you wear this?
But you and I look the most alike.
Yes, Ayumi and I look alike in the pink knit.
And the skirt with Mitsuki.
I went to a fan's room today.
I heard that the weather was bad at all the IAJOY events.
It did rain yesterday.
Yes, it did.
Then I heard something really loud... the sound of rain.
The sound of rain.
I think it's great that it cleared up a few times.
That's true. - Yeah.
It's been a great two days.
Was it nice meeting you all?
Thank you very much.
What?
What? Is that what I think it is?
Here, hold on.
Thank you.
Hi.
I was here earlier.
Okay, self-evaluate.
I'm Judy from Nearly Called Jew.
I'm Judy Hyde.
Ooh.
I'm Ayumi Ozawa, the second leader.
Leader?
Let's go that way.
Got it.
It's Moeko.
It's Moeko-san.
Moe! Moe!
Yay!
It's Moego-San!
Moeko-san's cute!
Sukizawa-san.
I like you every day.
You do?
Really?
I love it.
He's cute.
I said elephant.
It's Ozawa.
I changed it to "Ozawa" all by myself.
Yay!
I like it.
Reg.
Mr. Nanae.
It's Mr. 7th.
I forced myself to do it.
Choco Manaka.
And they're two very energetic people.
Ooh!
I'm a fan.
Oh!
Yay!
Mr. Seventh Day
Choco Manaka.
It's so bad that they are the same mask!
What do you two say?
Jyurin
Ai Jyurin
Yamamomo jan!
Yamamomojan!
You know, like, "Moemoe"?
Do you know what a fir tree is?
Today...
Nice to meet you!
I chose "like".
That's fine.
Hide it.
It smells so good.
Look at that.
You're cute, too, Moeko.
She's already here.
Hana no san's...
I can't show you anymore.
With the three of us like this...
No, I've never seen them before.
Daddy's going.
Thank you.
I tried.
Oh, you did?
I bought you a T-shirt.
That's great. Thank you.
I bought it today.
Thank you.
Thank you for wearing them.
Congratulations.
Girl talk.
Embarrassing.
This is too much.
What's so great about this place?
It's good, right?
Yay!
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
It's hard, definitely use it!
Please use it!
Yes, for four minutes.
I just finished a 4-minute talk.
I'm so happy that so many people came!
I did this house-in by myself today.
Don't you think I'm good at it?
I also put a lot of sparkles on today!
It's on the "Yujiyuhi" channel. Please let me know if you got it!
Today's fashion point?
Today's fashion point is...
You can't see the bottom. The most important point is the shoes.
I wore a red top, so I paired it with red heels.
Also, scarves seem to be in fashion, so I wrapped a scarf around my head.
But I thought it was a little too European, so I wrapped it around my waist.
But...
I was told by a fan that I don't know how to wrap a shoe scarf around my head.
I'll be careful.
Thank you very much.
Tell us what you ate and did today.
Well, I ate a cup of ramen today.
At home.
But then I went to this restaurant and got a box lunch.
I ate... again.
I ate too much.
Oh, yes...
I tried to look a little more grown up today.
I put on a beret.
Does it look good on me?
Here it comes!
Good morning!
Chanel, would you mind?
I won't bother you.
Oh, I see.
He likes me so much.
Oh, my gosh!
I've been captured!
I've memorized it for a day!
Bye-bye!
You're early!
Sorry. Sorry.
Don't go, Flash.
I see.
Here we go.
Okay.
Don't go, Flash.
Bye-bye.
Help me.
I got one more dongbis today.
What?
What do you mean?
Just do it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. I need my peeps.
You're wearing it.
It's cute.
It's cute. It's cute.
It's so cute!
I'll wear it, too.
I'll wear it.
Well, you're good at it!
You're good.
I'll put it on.
put it on
give it to him
good, good!
deyoshi!
Good!
Cute!
SKY-H
Poor little girl.
Stop it.
Oh, this is cute.
Really cute.
Oh, no.
It's cute.
It was too cute just now.
Who, who, who
I was whispering earlier.
She's cute.
You're so cute.
Hey, wait.
I sure hope you work hard.
You can take a picture, too.
I'll take a picture of the two of you together, then you go ahead.
You're so cute.
Hey, the back side of this Eziai.
I never get tired of looking at it.
Easy, easy, easy
I can't understand a word you're saying.
How do they talk to each other?
I'm curious!
Let's do it.
Erotic?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, here it comes.
You sure?
That's nice.
I love it. It's so cute.
Wow, fireworks!
Wamemaru
So cute!
I love Wamemaru!
Yay!
Fireworks!
Thank you very much.
Fireworks.
Here it comes.
Ismahans.
Yay.
I'm full of this.
I'm full.
Oh, my God.
This is so fun!
Yay!
Fireworks!
Yeah!
Yay!
Kitty cat
Yay
Jure Sea
In front of
Ne, wow, cute!
Ah ольш мер
Sitting
Cute
Very cute
Foot standing over there
Peach is cute.
Can I cut it off?
Peach is cute!
Seriously, it's cute.
Momojyu's cute!
Peach is cute.
Momo is cute
Peach cute
From the end
Peach is cute
Please reflect
Cute.
I like the coloring.
It's Oushioichan!
It's Ohshi-ohichan.
It's a bull.
It's like a pre-chrome.
Three, two, one.
Stylish
Cute
Pink
I see... cute all over.
Bear.
It's a bear.
A fan just told me.
He's so cute!
Yay!
I'm so happy to be able to talk to you seniors like this.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for crying.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Well, I hope to see you all again.
Three, two, one.
Pasha.
Bye-bye.
Please come closer.